{
    "subject": "resource/Matt_Blair",
    "predicate": "ontology/college",
    "object": "resource/Iowa_State_University",
    "human_readable": "Matt Blair attended Iowa State University.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9823518395423889,
            "question": "Is Matt Blair a graduate of Iowa State University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9499351978302002,
            "question": "Was Iowa State University Matt Blair's place of learning?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9192883968353271,
            "question": "In what state is the university Matt Blair attended located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9169261455535889,
            "question": "Where did Matt Blair attend university?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.802834689617157,
            "question": "To which university did Matt Blair go?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7629731893539429,
            "question": "Did Matt Blair study at a state-run university?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7315489649772644,
            "question": "What university is Matt Blair associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6873315572738647,
            "question": "Name the institution Matt Blair studied at."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5980446338653564,
            "question": "What university did Matt Blair complete his studies at?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3807753026485443,
            "question": "What is Matt Blair's educational background?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Matt Blair attended Iowa State University.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6575_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What university did Matt Blair complete his studies at?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6575_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the institution Matt Blair studied at.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6575_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What university is Matt Blair associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6575_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6575_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6575_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6575_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6575_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6575_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6575_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6575_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6575_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6575_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6575_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can confirm that the triple is supported by the documents.\n\nHere is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention Matt Blair attending Iowa State prior to the 1971 season after a brief stint at Northeast Oklahoma Junior College (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6575/re-ranker-msmarco/37.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6575/re-ranker-msmarco/77.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Matt Blair attended and played football for Iowa State University, supporting the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}